{
    "type": "simple-quiz",
    "title": "Emoji Raten",
    "rules": [
        "Gesucht ist ein Song, dargestellt durch Emojis",
        "Das Team, das ihn zuerst errÃ¤t, ruft die korrekte Antwort",
        "Das schnellere Team gewinnt"
    ],
    "instances": {
        "template": {
            "title": "Emoji Raten (Template)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "FRAGE",
                    "answer": "ANTWORT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "FRAGE",
                    "answer": "ANTWORT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "FRAGE",
                    "answer": "ANTWORT"
                }
            ],
            "randomizeQuestions": true
        },
        "v1": {
            "_players": [
                "St, Ju, Th, Sa, Ju",
                "An, Ko, Li, Th"
            ],
            "randomizeQuestions": true,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ§Š ğŸ§Š ğŸ‘¶",
                    "answer": "Ice Ice Baby â€“ Vanilla Ice",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/ice-ice-baby.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸªµ",
                    "answer": "Holz - 257ers",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/holz.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ’ƒ ğŸ‘‘",
                    "answer": "Dancing Queen â€“ ABBA",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/dancing-queen.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘ï¸ ğŸ”¥",
                    "answer": "I See Fire â€“ Ed Sheeran",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/i-see-fire.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘‹",
                    "answer": "Hello â€“ Adele",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/hello.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸš€ ğŸ‘¨",
                    "answer": "Rocket Man â€” Elton John",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/rocketman.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "â¤ï¸ ğŸ“–",
                    "answer": "Love Story â€” Taylor Swift",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/love-story.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ›£ï¸ â¡ï¸ ğŸ”¥",
                    "answer": "Highway to Hell â€” AC/DC",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/highway-to-hell.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸŒ§ï¸ ğŸ‘¨ğŸ‘¨ğŸ‘¨",
                    "answer": "Itâ€™s Raining Men â€” The Weather Girls",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/its-raining-men.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ¦ ğŸ’¤",
                    "answer": "The Lion Sleeps Tonight â€” The Tokens",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/the-lion-sleeps-tonight.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸŒ«ï¸ ğŸŒŠ",
                    "answer": "Smoke on the Water â€” Deep Purple",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/smoke-on-the-water.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ•º 5ï¸âƒ£",
                    "answer": "Mambo No. 5 â€” Lou Bega",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/mambo-nr-five.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘Š ğŸ›£ï¸ ğŸ™ğŸ»â€â™‚ï¸",
                    "answer": "Hit the Road Jack â€” Ray Charles",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/hit-the-road-jack.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘ï¸ â¤ï¸ ğŸ¸",
                    "answer": "I Love Rock â€™nâ€™ Roll â€” Joan Jett & The Blackhearts",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/i-love-rocknroll.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸŸª ğŸŒ§ï¸",
                    "answer": "Purple Rain â€” Prince",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/purple-rain.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ¦¶ ğŸš«",
                    "answer": "Footloose â€” Kenny Loggins",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/footloose.m4a"
                }
            ]
        },
        "v2": {
            "_players": [
                "Rob, Fab, Tin, Jo, Ste, Den, PhL"
            ],
            "randomizeQuestions": true,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ§Š ğŸ§Š ğŸ‘¶",
                    "answer": "Ice Ice Baby â€“ Vanilla Ice",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/ice-ice-baby.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘ƒ ğŸ‘¦ ğŸ‘»",
                    "answer": "Smells like Teen Spirit â€” Nirvana",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/smells-like-teen-spirit.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ§Ÿ ğŸ§Ÿ ğŸ§Ÿ ğŸ§Ÿ",
                    "answer": "Thriller - Michael Jackson",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/thriller.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸƒ ğŸ™‚",
                    "answer": "Poker Face - Lady Gaga",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/pokerface.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸŒ",
                    "answer": "Africa - Toto",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/africa.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ“… ğŸ”™",
                    "answer": "Yesterday - The Beatles",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/yesterday.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ  â˜€ï¸",
                    "answer": "House of the Rising Sun - The Animals",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/house-of-the-rising-sun.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ§ ğŸª",
                    "answer": "Man in the Mirror - Michael Jackson",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/man-in-the-mirror.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ¤ â˜”ï¸",
                    "answer": "Singin in the Rain - Gene Kelly",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/singin-in-the-rain.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ¤œ â˜ï¸â˜ï¸â˜ï¸ ğŸšª",
                    "answer": "Knockin' on Heavenâ€™s Door - Bob Dylan",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/knockin-on-heavens-door.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ¸ ğŸ«µ ğŸŒªï¸",
                    "answer": "Rock You Like a Hurricane - Scorpions",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/rock-you-like-a-hurricane.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸŒ ğŸ¶",
                    "answer": "Earth Song - Michael Jackson",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/earth-song.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸ‘¶ â˜ï¸ ğŸ•–",
                    "answer": "Baby One More Time - Britney Spears",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/baby-one-more-time.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "â›ˆï¸ ğŸ¯",
                    "answer": "Thunderstruck - AC/DC",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/thunderstruck.m4a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ğŸš¶ â˜€ï¸",
                    "answer": "Walking on Sunshine - Katrina and the Waves",
                    "answerAudio": "audio/emoji/v2/walking-on-sunshine.m4a"
                }
            ]
        }
    }
}
